in seunggeun-chi-963050153 | ➢ Seunggeun Chi

## Research Interests

My research interests lie in Machine Learning and its applications to real-world problems. Representation Learning in Computer Vision problems is my primary study. My research also spans over Combinatorial Optimization problems which aim to extract rules by applying Reinforcement Learning.

### **Education**

**Purdue University** West Lafayette, U.S.

Ph.D. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2021 - current

• C-Design Lab, Advisor: Karthik Ramani

**Seoul National University** Seoul, S.Korea

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2021

• Optimization Lab, Advisor: ByungRo Moon

• Computer Architecture Lab, Advisor: SangLyul Min

**Seoul National University** Seoul, S.Korea

Mar. 2013 - Feb. 2019 B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

## **Publications**

#### **Conference Proceedings**

- S. Chi\*, H. Chi\*, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023, submitted
- S. Chi\*, H. Chi\*, S. Chan, K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation. IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA), 2023, submitted
- [C2] H. Chi, M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022
- [C1] M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Y. Cha, B. R. Moon. Evolution-based Meta Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Optimization. In proceedings of the 23rd The Genetic and Evolutionary Computation Conference (GECCO), 2021

# Research & Project

#### Skeleton-based action sequence generation with salient atomic actions

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

July. 2020 - Sept. 2020

Dec. 2022 -

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- Encode latent action trajectory with Neural ODE.
- · Extract the salient action frames of actions, and define atomic actions with the salient action frames.
- Apply diffusion model to generate continuous action sequences with atomic actions.

#### **Weakly Supervised Action Segmentation for Video**

- Introduced a loss function for video segmentation combining Triplet loss and Temporal Cycle Consistency Loss
- Defined the Action Segmentation problem as a Neural Machine Translation problem

· Visualized the attention matrices to interpret Machine's inference

### Improving Multi-Joint dynamics with Contact(MuJoCo) by applying Hierarchical **Reinforcement Learning**

OptLab, Seoul National Univ.

OptLab, Seoul National Univ.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Sep. 2019 - Jul. 2020

- · Proposed a hierarchical architecture to give the agent frequent reward signals by setting subgoals
- Designed and developed a hierarchical architecture of model and environment
- Applied policy gradient with self-critical sequence training in optimization

#### Predicting stock price by applying Combinatorial Optimization

Jan. 2019 - Jun. 2019

- Analyzed data with the ANOVA(Analysis of variance) method and Regression method
- · Applied Genetic Algorithm, Evolutional Computation, and Fourier transformation to find better solutions
- Applied distributed computing to accelerate independent computation

#### Accelerating computation of Machine Learning by using Field-Programmable Gate Array

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Aug. 2018 - Jan. 2019

- · Applied methods of SIMD(Single Instruction Multiple Data) with the low-level language of Verilog
- Reduced data size with SVD(Singular Value Decomposition)
- Rearranged units to utilize parallel computation

#### Designing spatial-navigation on chrome-extension

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- formulated malfunctioning cases and defined user-friendly environment
- Developed user-friendly navigation UI
- https://github.com/WICG/spatial-navigation

Skills

**Research and Development Stacks** 

**Major Languages** Python, C/C++, java, Verilog Machine Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow **Computer Vision** OpenCV, OpenGL

Web Languages Nginx, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS

Database MySQL, SQLite

**Other Tools and Skills** 

Other Langauges Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab, R **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

**Text Editors & IDE** Vim, VSCode, Eclipse Software SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

VCS Git

**Working Experience** 

**SK Hynix** Icheon, S.Korea

Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2017 INTERN RESEARCHER

· Designed an exclusive chip for testing 3D NAND flash architecture and verified the reliabilty of existing architectures

• Developed a module for predicting locality of data and tested it with real data

**Korean National Police Agency** 

Dokdo, S.Korea

DOKDO SECURITY POLICE Dec. 2013 - Sep. 2015

· Defended the disputed territory as a squad leader

# **Teaching Experience**

CS.4190.681A	Genetic Algorithm, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.407	Algorithm, 2019-fall, 2020-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.M1522.407	<b>Data Structure</b> , 2019-spring, 2020-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.308	Computer architecture, 2018-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.035.001	<b>Digital Computer Concept and Practice</b> , 2017-fall, 2018-fall	Teaching Assistant
PE.051.004	Volley ball, 2018-fall, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant

## **Honors & Awards**

#### Competition of accelerating General-Purpose GPU sponsored by Intel

Manycore Programming Lab

1ST PLACE

Korea Ministry of Science and ICT

Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021

#### The National Scholarship for Science and Engineering

FULL SCHOLARSHIP